<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on u915</title>
    <link>https://u915.net/tags/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on u915</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2020 — u915 —</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://u915.net/tags/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Shell script to push content to Github pages</title>
      <link>https://u915.net/posts/2020/09/shell-script-to-push-content-to-github-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://u915.net/posts/2020/09/shell-script-to-push-content-to-github-pages/</guid>
      <description>This post is about how to make a simple shell script to push content to Github.
The goal is to automate the process of posting into my blog on Github pages.
Note: This script assumes that the git folder contains an already init git.
Creating a new file named pusher.sh
Permissions:
chmod +x pusher.sh  #!/bin/bash PATH_BLOG=/awesome/path/* PATH_GIT=/awesome/path TIMESTAMP=`date +&#39;%Y-%m-%d %H:%M:%S&#39;` USER=&amp;quot;awesomeUser&amp;quot; REPO=&amp;quot;awesomeRepo&amp;quot; BRANCH=&amp;quot;master&amp;quot; cp -R ${PATH_BLOG} ${PATH_GIT} cd ${PATH_GIT} git add --all .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Host a static web using Github pages, custom domain and https</title>
      <link>https://u915.net/posts/2020/09/host-a-static-web-using-github-pages-custom-domain-and-https/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://u915.net/posts/2020/09/host-a-static-web-using-github-pages-custom-domain-and-https/</guid>
      <description>This post is about how to host a static web site on Github pages, using a custom domain and HTTPS.
Static site First a static web site prepared to be deployed on any host.
Note: remember, a static web site is not using php, pythom, asp etc is only html,css and js. Dynamic content will not work
Github account Second, a Github account to create a new public repository. This repository will be special because is designed to have one per free account and are limited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello world, how to create a new static web site blog using Hugo</title>
      <link>https://u915.net/posts/2020/09/hello-world-how-to-create-a-new-static-web-site-blog-using-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 19:51:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://u915.net/posts/2020/09/hello-world-how-to-create-a-new-static-web-site-blog-using-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Instead to make another Hello world page or enumerating the reasons of writting a new blog, this is a writeup of how this site was build. Is a good way to make the first page useful and serve as work a memory. Maybe i can help me or someone in the future.
Choosing CMS  Learn something new Durable and easy to maintain Portable Simple Secure ?  Technology involved This site is based of using static plain text files written in Markdown.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>